No animals were hurt during the
production of this video.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Go!
Go! Go!
Search around!
He is wounded!
He can't go too far!
I have to go.
The mine!
To the mine!
People!
Hear me out!
Ertugrul Ghazi's son Kayi's Bey Osman Bey...
...is a rebel guilty!
He disobeyed Seljuq
He run away from the judge.
He'll be punished when he is found!
Hear me out!
Watch who you are talking about!
Osman Bey wouldn't do such a thing!
Vizier Alam-shah!
What you are doing to Osman Bey
is not Turkish tradition.
Malhun Hatun.
Umur Bey's beloved daughter.
The mother of Osman Bey's heir.
I am so sorry to see you under
these conditions.
Your face says how sorry you are, really.
Don't tire yourself.
No, no. I really am sorry.
Because I believe Osman Bey is innocent.
But why would someone like Osman Bey...
...run away from the judgment...
...even without denying the accusations?
Obviously, there is something he hides.
My Bey does everything on a purpose.
I have no doubt that he is innocent.
Osman Bey and I experienced
many troubles.
And we know how to get rid of them.
Don't worry about that.
You are going to remember these days,
Vizier Alam Shah.
Hadrat Vizier.
The announcers yell that Osman Bey
is a betrayer...
...as you ordered.
Then it is time to visit Kayi tents.
O The Healer!
They couldn't take Osman Bey to Konya.
He got rid of them.
But where is he now?
What is he doing?
Don't worry, daughter.
No one should worry.
We will overcome this
with Allah's permission.
We will for sure.
Also, Osman wouldn't go with the men
of that Vizier...
...if he hadn't had a plan.
He must have a plan.
The first thing I'll do is to...
...go to Konya to see Sultan Mesut.
I have to talk about what
all of this is about.
Before we understand what's going on,
they are going to come at us as they see..
...the empty throne of Kayi.
However, Osman Bey will solve
this problem as well.
Kayi's throne cannot stay empty!
Give me patience, the messenger of Allah!
Vizier Alam-shah is coming!
Mari! My dear wife!
You look better.
The Turkish dress was awful!
It was terrible!
You looked like a shepherd!
But now...
...look at you!
You are like a real princess.
What makes a human powerful and honorable
is not their dress, Nicola.
That Osman and Turgut and all
who you cannot defeat...
...their source for power is here.
But you don't have that.
You will never be the man I want.
Where are you now, Mari?
You are in my castle.
You are with me.
Those men who you think powerful...
...didn't even realise
while I was getting you!
This is power, you get it?
This is pure power!
Is it enough?
No, it's not!
More power!
More! More!
Where is Kornelia?
I asked around, no one saw her.
She is resting.
My dear wife Mari.
This is our first dinner.
I have a very special
meal prepared for you.
The most special meal I'll eat...
...is the meal I'll eat with you
for the last time, Nicola.
What was your friend's name?
Kornia... no no!
Kornelia!
Well-cooked Kornelia.
The barrels are burning!
There is a fire!
Run!
Fire!
Bring water!
Run!
It's Turkish tradition.
The throne, the position of Bey
cannot be empty.
The owner of the throne...
...the Bey of the tribe is still alive.
Thank Allah.
When the situation changes...
...we'll start talking about this.
Sheik Edebali.
You are absolutely right.
But we are not in a peace era.
The enemy surrounded us.
The Lords are greedy.
What are you trying to say, Alam shah?
Make the long story short.
Say what you have to say.
You are right, old woman.
Let's make the long story short.
While Osman Bey is absent...
Someone needs to sit on the throne.
And that person is Gündüz Bey.
As my Sheik said...
...Osman Bey is alive.
No one else is needed.
It's not the right time to talk about this,
Vizier Alam shah.
This is unnecessary now
It is apparent that you misunderstood me.
I am not asking.
I am ordering.
Inegol Castle.
I'll kill you!
How can you do this?
What did you think, Mari, huh?
Did you think I was really in love with you?
What did you think?
I was going to marry you only for
political issues! Only for political issues!
I'll kill you!
But what did you do?
You humiliated me.
You humiliated me!
You dishonored me!
I don't forget, Mari!
I don't forget, understand? I don't!
I just wait!
My dear wife.
Goodbye.
Mari.
Turgut!
It's okay.
Hang on.
Come on!
Get me out of here!
Save me!
Please save me!
Get me out of here!
Kornelia!
Are you okay?
- Thank God.
- We are here to save you.
Where is Lord's room?
There are many soldiers outside!
Follow me.
Let's go.
Your death is here Nicola!
I am your death!
Turgut!
Mari.
- Mari!
- Hurry up my Bey! They're coming!
The secret passage.
Take this to the secret passage, Kutay.
Come on! Come on!
Let's go, come on!
You'll be fine, Mari.
Let's go!
Go go!
Don't let them get away!
Soldier!
Hold the doors!
Leave me!
Go hold the doors shut!
The doors!
Mari, wake up, Mari!
- Kornelia!
- Mari!
Go, go!
Where is Kutay?
- Go!
Run! Run!
Hold the doors shut!
Leave me!
Come here.
Mari!
She is waking up!
You are fine, right?
You are fine.
- Tugrut.
- I am here.
I am here.
My Bey, we have no time.
They'll find us.
Okay, we are leaving.
Hold Mari.
Easy, easy.
Bring Mari.
Come on!
Come on, easy, easy.
Come mari, easy.
Thank Allah.
Gündüz Bey, my Bey trusted you!
Now instead of looking for him, you are
taking his place!
You are talking to your Bey, Malhun Hatun!
Hear yourself.
Osman became a rebel.
You were there too.
I obeyed.
What would happen if I revolted too?
-Vizier Alemşah--
-He is setting Osman up!
Don't you see this?
Vizier is doing his duty.
He wants to do nothing but help.
People are happy since he came.
He is helping the tribes, keeping peace
with the Lords.
Isn't this bloodshed is enough,
Malhun Hatun?
Do you ever learn from the past, Gündüz?
Vizier is trying to break the tribe apart.
Look, you are there...
...we are here.
He already broke us.
Do you know where and how your brother is?
Mother...
...Osman revolted against the Sultan.
He is running.
I am here for the sake of my tribe.
What about Osman?
You think about the tribe
but not your brother.
Where and how Osman is?
Did you get drunk in power?
You are going too far, Malhun Hatun!
Osman is my brother.
I love him more than any of you do.
But Konya's order is clear.
I am trying to keep my tribe safe.
Then, Gündüz Bey...
...first, go after Mari who was
taken from our tribe.
Our guest got kidnapped.
Tell me, who did this?
Bala is right.
If you sit on the throne...
...then first, find the traitor among us.
After that, take my Osman's valiant
alps...
...from the Vizier.
They are Kayı's alps.
They are innocent.
Hatuns!
It is time for us to leave.
Gündğz Bey has a lot of work to do.
Gündüz...
...what will we do now?
Is it the right thing to trust the Vizier?
I did what I did...
...for my tribe, Ayşe.
You keep an eye on Malhun and Bala.
They won't stay still.
My Vizier...
...we followed Osman for a long
while but...
...we lost his track in the dark.
We surrendered the woods.
I will go back at the first light.
He is wounded.
He has nowhere to go.
Good.
I don't want any mistakes, Konur.
Osman will be beheaded as he is seen.
His reputation will fade with him.
Also, anyone who helps
Osman Bey will be beheaded.
As you order, my Vizier.
Ferman.
These Kayı people can do anything.
They will try everything to get to Osman.
Watch the tribe closely.
I want Gündüz Bey and the Lords
at the inn.
As you order, Vizier.
The rebels' blood...
...will feed the order I establish.
In this order...
...only those who bow to me will stand.
My Creator.
My Creator
My Allah, my Allah!
Thank you.
My Creator.
My merciful Creator.
My Creator, You...
...You didn't let me stay
hungry and thirsty.
You didn't, my Creator.
I cannot honor my debt...
...no matter how many times I thank you...
...many times until I cannot speak anymore...
...I still cannot honor my debt.
I can't, my Creator.
My Allah.
How great is your mercy!
Hey Enlightened Creator!
Praise be to Allah.
I'll take revenge for you, Gonca.
But I have to find my Bey first.
I have to find my Bey.
Boran.
Don't leave, Boran.
Even if I am angry with him,
I still need to find my Bey, Gonca.
Don't leave.
Don't leave, Boran.
I won't, Gonca.
I am not leaving anywhere.
Soldiers! Go!
He is in this direction
according to the tracks.
Soldiers, go!
You are cornered, Osman Bey!
I found you Osman.
Where can you run?
Hold it, hold it!
Take it.
Soldiers! This way!
He is wounded!
He cannot go too far.
I know it is not the right time.
But tell me.
Who abducted you?
I don't know.
I was fainted.
I was in a chest when I woke up.
Didn't you see anyone?
Do you remember anyone?
Seljuk Soldiers...
...they're the ones who turned me over.
Alemshah,...
...snake!...
...Snake!.
I will make you pay for this!
And a sherbet...
...Ayse Hatun brought me sherbet
and gave me to drink it...
...I don't remember the rest.
Then, Gündüz...
...Gündüz Bey is in cahoots
with the Vizier.
Why?
What's the reason Gündüz?
Nobody is around my Bey,
they lost our track...
- ...we can go now.
- Let's go then, Kutan.
Let's go so that Osman Bey can
know about the traitor in his tribe.
I'm going to go to the Kayı
tents. You be careful.
You never know what that
weasel Nikola will do.
Yes, my Bey.
Alps! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- I'm here.
I'm here.
I'm with you.
I won't leave you.
Alright, you may go.
Ergus, is there a trace?
There is no trace sir.
We just got the word, that Vizier
Alemshah is waiting for you.
That's just what we need at this moment.
Look at the state I am.
Kosses is probably there too.
Kosses should never know of this Ergus!
Never!
I don't have time and patience for this!
Sir, what if Kosses already knows?
We'd know of it if that
was the case.
I will act accordingly.
It's not Kosses that matters...
...he is easy,...
...Vizier Alemshah.
Let's see what Vizier
Alemshah's problem is.
Let's go!
They came with a bunch of soldiers.
They said that coal, now
belongs to Seljuk.
It's Vizier's order.
He'll gather the Turkmen Beys
at the willow.
I'd like you to come with me.
We'll talk about this as well.
Vizier caused a lot of trouble
to Osman Bey.
I don't trust the Vizier, Gündüz Bey.
Davut Agha, for now Vizier's
intent is sincere.
You should listen to him yourself.
Alright, I'll come.
Let's see what he wants.
How dare you come to our tribe!
Message from Sultan Mesud.
Son of Ertuğrul Ghazi Osman Bey has
disobeyed the orders of Sultan Mesud...
...and became a rebel.
That is why when Osman Bey is caught,
instead of bringing him on horseback...
...he'll be dragged from the rear of the
horse all the way to Konya.
Also...
...if anyone tries to help Osman Bey...
- ...their heads will be...
- Enough!
This is Kaya Tribe!
We are humble servants of the state...
...you did not have to come all this way.
If I find Osman Bey, I'll take
him to Sultan myself.
We made the right call coming
here Gündüz Bey...
...wanted the give you the news ourselves.
Godspeed!
They couldn't find Osman, mother.
Thank Allah, my girl...
...thank Allah!
Everyone get back to work!
There is nothing to see here.
Move on!
If you see Osman or know where he is...
...tell me about it.
I'll save my brother.
Come to Gündüz Bey if that
is the case.
Don't worry about it Gündüz Bey.
Osman Bey will know who to contact to.
Don't worry about it.
Mahun Hatun,...
...Boran Alp...
...you won't take him with you?
Boran is not on the
right frame of mind.
He doesn't even know where
to stop. Don't you see?
Ayşe,...
...we don't know what Hatuns will do.
If they leave the tribe, tell me about it.
Of course, my Bey.
Aygül, it's time to go.
Tribe and Orhan is in your hands.
Mother, give me your blessing.
You may have my blessing my girl...
...If Allah permits, come back safe.
May Allah keep you safe.
Don't keep us unaware.
Thank you, Bala.
These are Vizier Alemshah's men.
What are they doing at the tribe?
We'll enter from somewhere else Mari,
come on.
Ayşe Hatun,
I was looking for you...
Mother, I got some business to attend
to, let's talk later.
I know how good your engravings are...
...mine aren't as pretty as yours.
Can you show me how to do it?
Okay, I'll show you.
What are you up to Ayşe Hatun?
Come on!
Come on.
Mari, Turgut Bey, hope you're both okay.
- Malhun Hatun
- Mari?
You're wounded!
Slowly, slowly!
If Allah permits, she'll be alright.
I saw Vizier's men at the tribe.
- Is everything okay?
- Unfortunately, no.
Vizier tricked Osman Bey...
...Osman Bey is now a fugitive...
...we are looking for him.
We can't go to the tribe then.
You can make it Mari.
I'll make it.
We are coming too.
Do you know where Osman Bey is?
No, we don't.
We'll look everywhere.
Kumral Abdal will help us.
Alright then, let's go.
Let's go.
It looks like they'll go to Osman Bey.
Come on.
We'll follow them like a shadow.
We're coming close.
This way!
What are you running from?
Who are you?
Osman.
Dark Osman?
Bey Osman?
Someone's coming!
Are they after you or me?
Why would they be after a shepherd?
It looks like they're after you.
Osman Bey,...
...hide.
I found you, Osman Bey.
Did a wounded man pass here?
I said, did a wounded man pass here?
I'd be lying if I said anything.
Maybe he passed...
...but I didn't see him.
Maybe he didn't pass but I thought he did.
I do not know.
Don't play word games shepherd!
Did you see him or not?
Maybe what I saw was more than a man...
...maybe he has no manhood inside him.
You're asking the question
wrong soldier agha.
- What is your name?
- Why do you want to know my name?
I'm just a shepherd...
...they call me shepherd.
Listen up, shepherd!
If you lie to me, I'll butcher you
with my sword!
Let's go!
Stop!
It was old, used to slow the herd.
I was right about to skin it.
Soldiers, let's move!
Don't give up.
Osman Bey
Be careful.
Let me help.
You did a great thing.
- Thank you.
- Thank you too.
Come with me my Bey.
Hang on my Bey!
Hang on!
Careful my Bey.
There it is.
This is my ration my Bey.
No, no
- It is yours.
- My bey,
It is yours brother
If you take half it'll multiply.
I will not forget your help.
Humans are flawed...
...people forget my bey...
Allah is the greatest!
I live for the people and do everything
for the people my Bey.
How do you know I am a man
of the people?
Maybe I'm one of the tyrants.
What if they were looking for
me for a crime?
How do you know?
Even if I don't know, these
animals know my Bey.
They can smell it.
They could have drawn attention
on you but...
...they shushed my Bey.
They did not make a noise.
They sheltered you.
They protected you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you too, my bey.
Wherever you go they'll find you.
But no one would think looking
at a shepherd's barracks.
At Koryan's...
...mountainside, I have a place...
...go there my bey.
Thank you.
If I overcome this trouble...
You will my bey, you will.
High mountains will have denser mist.
I'll...
I'll never forget you.
Praise be!
Come at me!
Brother,...
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for Osman Bey.
Who is this Osman Bey?
Why are you looking for him?
He fights the infidels...
...protects the weak.
Why would I not look for
a bey like that agha?
Then,...
...he is right in front of you.
No,...
...no need for that brother.
No need for that.
The bow that is stretched,...
...the arrow that's stuck,...
...stolen equipment....
...is at your command Osman Bey.
State your name.
It's Durahan, my bey.
I am at your command.
You are not from here
that much is clear.
Where do you come from?
I come from Caucasia my bey.
Praise be!
Caucasia is famous for its eagles
and valiants.
Thank you!
Welcome!
Thank you.
You're with me now.
Let's go.
Come on.
Did anyone pass here shepherd?
Let's go!
Is Osman Bey a traitor?
Why punish his helpers?
Is this fair, Alemshah?
It is fair Gündüz Bey.
He has accepted all the convictions
given to him by escaping.
Isn't disobeying Sultan's orders treason?
You are the son of Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Is your loyalty to Osman or your tribe?
My tribe.
I thought so too.
Keep an eye on your people.
We would not want anyone to get hurt.
Alps are Kayi alps.
When will you release them?
No Kayi alp is taken hostage.
The ones that are kept are Osman's alps.
Not Kayi alps.
If I release them they'll go after Osman
and burn themselves along with you.
I'll send them to Konya. They will
be at Sultan Mesut's hands.
If they don't do anything crazy
on their way over there...
...they will be spared Gündüz Bey.
We got more important things to talk about
It has to do with tribes future.
Vizier your excellence, The Lords are here.
How is Mari, Nikola?
Is she still angry?
Mari is my precious stone Kosses.
I'm doing everything I can to make
her feel good but...
...she is a bit, you know...
...- combative.
- Nikola,...
...she is angry at me.
Whatever mistake she may make,
she is my most precious.
She is a clever girl. She'll
understand us overtime.
I think we should give it some time.
Look, as I was returning from
Constantinople...
...Osman has become a traitor for Seljuk.
Vizier is on our side...
...and we're at the willow.
That's true. You are
correct, my saint friend.
Does it smell like victory?
Who would know I would be
right by Osman Bey, right bey?
Durahan stop!
Stop.
- Osman Bey!
- Turgut Bey.
Osman Bey.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I am fine. Don't worry.
Thankfully, thankfully, Osman Bey.
Come here.
My Osman!
Malhun!
Osman!
My Bey!
You are wounded.
Don't worry, I am fine.
- You are?
- I am. Don't worry.
How did you find me?
Good luck, brother.
No luck comes when you say it.
We are looking for a Bey.
Have you seen one, Çoban Agha?
If found by looking, everyone would find.
Why are you looking for him?
It doesn't matter why. Have you seen him
or not. It is urgent!
Malhun Hatun, let's not confuse him.
He won't talk that way.
Confuse.
I won't get confused.
Osman Bey.
Don't worry, brother.
We are his friends, that's why.
Now, tell us...
...where he went.
They are his friends.
This way.
He went to the Harmanlık way.
-But he was walking, hurry up.
-Thank you!
May Allah bless that shepherd.
Sit, let me take a look at your wound.
-Come here.
-Sit.
In the name of Allah!
Allah is the healer.
Thank you.
My Bey, we came prepared.
Osman Bey.
Turahan Alp.
Choose our road...
...and came after us.
From now on, he is my alp.
Also...
...I owe him my life.
My life is yours on this way, my Bey.
-May you be with us.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Come on, eat.
Friends.
Mari?
Are you well?
She is, now.
But that dog Nikola...
...wounded Mari, in front of my eyes.
But I am fine now.
How did that dog...
...kidnap you?
Tell me. We will not let anyone
get to you!
The last thing I remember is...
...the sherbet Ayşe Hatun brought.
I drank it.
When I woke up I was with the Vizier
Alemşah's men.
Then, Turgut came.
My Bey, Söğüt is confused.
Sultan Mesut told everyone he will behead
everyone who helps you.
That snake Vizier.
He poisoned Sultan too.
His aim was to make me alone.
But...
...there is something else.
Bala? Orhan?
How is the tribe?
Tell me!
How are they?
Gündüz Bey.
Vizier sat Gündüz Bey to your place,
my Bey.
Gündüz Bey is with the Vizier.
What are you saying?
My brother is with the Vizier.
Vizier Alemşah!
The Kayı Tribe's real bey...
...Gündüz Bey!
Here you go.
How many soldiers did you lose, Nikola?
Hundreds? Thousands?
What about you, Lords?
Rogatus?
Kosses?
What about you, you great Beys?
How many alps did you bury?
How many martyrs?
Si vis pacem, para bellum.
If you want peace, get ready for a war.
Forget about these lines, Lords.
I promise you peace without a war.
Now it is time to stop the bloodshed.
So, Vizier Alemşah.
How do you plan on doing that?
Since there is always a war on
these lands.
What is the situation of your subjects,
Nikola?
What about yours'?
What about you?
Is there abundance in your tribes?
There will be abundence.
There will be happiness.
This will provide peace.
Prosperity takes effort.
What is your plan?
This is why I called you.
We will establish a bazaar in İnegöl.
Many caravans will come from Konya and
Constantine...
...and buy your goods.
This trade will bring firstly abundance,
secondly peace...
...to our lands.
Thank you, Majesty.
We are pleased since you came.
Thanks to your presence, we can eat
and feed.
May you always be.
Amen! Amen!
Not at all!
It is Allah who gives sustenance.
We are just a means.
I hope to get the best of everything
for us...
...and for the Lords.
If the vizier Alemşah is the guarantor...
...we will take goods everywhere.
Gündüz Bey.
It is an honor for us to vouch for
a moral trader like you.
The traders who will work with you
are very lucky.
We will be incredibly strong together.
Amen!
-Amen.
-I hope so.
Gündüz Bey can have my place...
...if he wants to.
The sky will be a tent for me...
...the sun will be my fire...
...the ground will be my throne.
Wherever I am...
...is the state.
They martyred...
...Prophet Hüseyin.
For what?
For the throne!
Cain killed Abel.
For what?
Because of his ambition.
His jealousy.
Seljuk on one hand...
...Mogul on the other hand.
They are all listening to their demons.
All of them.
However...
...however, I...
...I pray Allah to not make me...
...a prisoner to my demons.
In the name of Allah!
My cause is not the title.
My cause is my love.
It is the red apple.
It is Allah's words.
It is spreading the word to
the whole world.
How great of you!
The lovers don't die!
If my brother is...
...more qualified...
...to carry out my cause...
...then he can.
But...
...if he breaks the cause...
...and succumbs to himself...
...if he tries to stab me in the back...
...like Cain did to Abel...
...then...
...then I won't care he is my brother.
And do what is necessary.
Osman Bey...
...I thought about this but didn't say it.
Obviously, who gave Mari to Nikola is
Gündüz.
I can't let this go without doing
anything.
I told you I'll do what is necessary,
Turgut Bey.
I've never left any cruelty,
any injustice...
...without punishment.
I even beheaded my uncle...
...to ensure justice.
For justice, I won't hesitate to behead...
...even my brother.
Thank you.
My Bey, I have some more news.
The alps.
My Bey, the alps.
They are taking the alps to Konya for
hearing tomorrow.
In that case...
...we will save the alps first.
Tomorrow is the most suitable time...
...to go to Konya.
No.
We will go to Söğüt first.
We will take our alps while
the Vizier is there.
We will destroy...
..that Vizier's reputation.
Now, listen to me carefully.
-Slowly, my Bey.
-Slowly!
Malhun...
...you go to my Sheik.
Tell them to do the belt ceremony for
then Ahis.
Call that snake Vizier too.
Call him so that he gets distracted.
He will think all the Söğüt is obeying
him.
In the meantime, we will save our alps.
As you order, my Bey.
Aygül.
Go to the tribe, talk to Bala.
Keep an eye on...
...my brother and Ayşe Hatun.
I want to know what is going on
in the tribe.
As you order, my Bey.
-Baysungur!
-Yes, my Bey?
Get the horses ready.
As you order, my Bey.
Kumral Abdal, you will inform Kosses.
His sister is with us.
She is safe, he doesn't need to worry.
After what Nikola did to Mari...
...he will want revenge.
As you order, my Bey.
As our enemy is the same...
...Kosses will want to fight with us.
If the safety of the roads is ensured and
where the market will be is finalized...
...everyone will get stronger and richer.
As I understood, Vizier Alemşah...
...our friend Nikola...
...will have more power than us...
...and will get richer than us.
For sure, Kosses. For sure.
Say what you want to say, Lords.
Why not Harmankaya...
...or Bilecik?
Why only İnegöl?
Not only İnegöl.
One month in Söğüt, one month in İnegöl.
If Nikola is ready to make sacrifices...
...we can establish them also
in Harmankaya or Bilecik.
No need for more talking.
It is time for action.
Everyone knows their duty.
Let's get to work.
The Lords freaked out when they heard...
...that the bazaar will be in İnegöl.
But there will be only one, Gündüz Bey.
It is about time they attack each other.
Winning is this easy.
We will shatter the infidels
from the inside...
...without even touching our sword.
Moguls are waiting to attack.
First, we must deal with these.
Then, we will be altogether against
the enemy.
I hope so.
My Bey.
Have you asked the actual question?
What will happen to the mines?
You are right, Master Davut.
They say Kayı's mine now belongs to
the Seljuks.
That mine is the result of the chaos
that Osman created.
We didn't give it to Nikola.
Be happy about this.
It now belongs to the Seljuks...
...to keep the order.
Alright.
Then, excuse us.
We couldn't find Osman, my Vizier.
But I sent soldiers all over the woods.
He has nowhere to go.
I will find him, my Vizier.
If you couldn't find him until now,
Konur...
...obviously, he will come to us.
His alps, Konur.
He will get ready to take them back.
We will be on full alert.
If he does as I say and comes...
...we will catch him.
Then, I will prepare for this, my Vizier.
When we deliver peace and prosperity...
...thanks to this bazaar...
...it won't take long...
...for people to forget about Osman...
...whose reputation is destroyed.
After I get the people's support...
...not the tribe...
...not the Söğüt...
...not the borders...
...but I will be the ruler of all
the Seljuk lands.
What about the Lords...
...Sir?
The Lords?
They are only pawns on this road.
Just like the Turkmens.
I will step on them when I want to.
Now, I am letting them win.
Bala, girl!
Stop drawing circles. My head is
getting dizzy. Sit and wait, please.
There is still no news, mother.
What if they couldn't find Osman?
Look at us!
Ah, my girl, ah!
Are you fine?
I am, mother. I am fine.
It is moving as if it understands.
Oh, my dear.
Can I come in?
Come in, Aygül!
We found Osman Bey, thankfully.
He is well.
Thankfully! Thankfully!
Thankfully!
Thank you, my Allah!
Where is he now?
He is really fine, right?
He is.
Turgut Bey and Mari is with him.
Turgut Bey took Mari back from Nikola.
Thankfully!
Now, listen to me carefully.
Osman Bey believes Gündüz Bey and
Ayşe Hatun...
...are involved in Mari's kidnapping.
What are you saying, Aygül?
How?
Do you remember the sherbet Ayşe Hatun
brought to Mari that night?
So?
Mari fainted after drinking.
The Vizier's soldiers took Mari to Nikola.
How could he?
Ah, Gündüz!
Couldn't we teach you anything?
How could you deliver our guest
to the enemy!
Ayşe Hatun!
She fooled us!
How could she, mother?
This is betrayal!
Osman Bey told us to keep an eye on Ayşe
Hatun and Gündüz Bey...
...but don't get them suspicios.
They will never know we saw Osman Bey.
No secret can be revealed.
Don't worry, my dear.
My Sheik, we will turn the tribe
upside down.
Osman Bey wants us to make
the belt ceremony...
...and gather the people.
He wants you to invite the Vizier too and
show him that you are his subject.
This is a war.
War is not just about weapons.
We will do what Osman Bey says, my girl.
Now, our weapon is our mind.
It is acceptable.
Thank you, my Sheik.
Now...
...let's invite the Vizier first.
Harmankaya Castle
I recognized you.
The madmen in the woods.
Madmen, huh?
Thankfully, I am.
I hope, I am.
You are Osman's madmen.
Rigth?
How dare you?
What kind of bravery is this?
You come to my castle alone.
Do you trust your Allah like the others?
To those who know how to look
can know everything.
Those who don't,
can't see what is in the open.
You can't see Allah by looking up.
You look at your heart to see.
You are too blind, Kosses.
You can't see even if you look.
But your blindness isn't permanent.
It will go away one day.
What are you telling, madmen?
Cut it short.
I came so you don't worry about
your sister Mari.
Her wound is getting better.
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
Mari is with Nikola.
No, Mari is not with her executioner.
Nikola tried to kill her but...
...Turgut Bey... What a valiant!
He saved your sister!
Now, she is with Osman Bey.
You!
What are you talking about?
I thought you were a smart man.
Did you believe that Nikola demon's word?
Nikola!
How long would you keep it a secret?
Taking revenge from Mari, huh?
Daring to kill my sister!
You will pay for this!
You will!
-Soldiers! Get ready!
-Stop.
Take a breath.
Osman Bey is waiting for you.
He said ''Kosses is a smart man.
He will see me before Nikola.''.
He is waiting for you.
Your secret will be revealed too, Kosses.
Turkish tribes will prosper, I hope.
We made a deal with our old friends,
the Lords and Vizier Alemşah.
A grand bazaar will be established
in İnegöl.
There is no such thing as an old friend.
Snake tongued Alemşah is poisoning you.
Open your eyes already!
You are talking to the Bey of the tribe,
mother.
He is the Bey of the tribe, mother.
I am talking to the Bey of the tribe,
right?
You are right.
I talk and talk but...
...his blind eyes can't see
what's right...
...or wrong.
Where is Osman Bey, Gündüz Bey?
How is he?
Are you worried for prosperity when you
don't know if your brother is alive?
Don't cross the line, Bala Hatun!
I don't want to break your heart.
But I am the Bey of Kayı!
We are here to talk about the future of
the Kayı!
I don't want to hear anything else!
The deal we made with Vizier Alemşah
will solve...
...all the problems of our people.
You still talk about trade, Vizier!
There is no Bey, no alp.
Master Davut!
My respect for your age is about to
run out!
What I say is for the sake of the whole
Turks.
We kept and kept fighting.
Shouldn't this tribe get better?
Shouldn't these people take a breath?
Can we come in?
Patience, patience.
Come in.
Sheik Edebalı sent his greetings,
Gündüz Bey.
There will be the belt ceremony in Söğüt
tomorrow.
Vizier Alemşah is one of our guests.
My Sheik expects you too.
I'd like to come, Akça Dervish.
But I will visit the new bazaar in İnegöl
tomorrow.
Next time.
Send my love to my Sheik.
I came to ask for permission.
If you allow, we would like to hold
a belt ceremony...
...for the journeymen's transition
to mastery tomorrow.
Of course!
How could we say no to our Sheik Edebalı?
You can, of course!
I would like to see you there...
...while our children get their mastery...
...Vizier Alemşah.
I am actually deeply honored.
And surprised.
Don't be. Now, me and all the other Ahis
are your subjects.
We want the whole Söğüt to see this.
Good!
Good, Sheik Edebalı!
I would love to be there.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
There is a lot of work to do.
Of course, here you go.
Thank you.
Edebalı is a very dangerous man, Konur.
It is obvious he is in contact with Osman.
They are playing a game.
I will let them play their game.
For now.
Tomorrow, while I am with Ahis...
...look sharp.
My Bey, I heard from the blacksmith.
Vizier is establishing a bazaar in İnegöl.
That vile Vizier's goal is to...
...get the Lords richer and...
...earn reputation.
It is against everything I do.
He is promising fake peace to people.
Can I come in?
Come in!
My Bey.
Come in.
Mari!
My sister!
Are you fine?
Mari, whom you left to Nikola and tried
to kill.
Did you just remember I am your sister?
Mari, I just--
Don't, Kosses!
Stay back.
Stop.
I just wanted you to have a good life.
I won't let that bastard Nikola get away
with what he has done.
I promise you, I will hurt him such that
...
Now we have a common enemy.
Whatever it takes.
Osman Bey.
I am ready to unite with you
to make their life a living hell.
There will be a belt ceremony in Söğüt.
If you are that sincere...
...you will get us into Söğüt.
Alright.
You will get into Söğüt without
any suspect.
Samuel will get you inside.
If you lose us...
...there will be no one left in these
lands.
Being alone means...
...being a prey.
I am neither a hunter nor a prey,
Osman Bey.
I am just a wounded man who has
been betrayed by his closest ones...
... and wants to avenge his sister.
You can trust me.
Stop!
Why are you here?
I brought the presents of Lord Kossess
for Vizier Alam Shah.
Let them pass!
- Salam Aleikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Seljuq's valiant soldiers!
All the Sogut drank this sherbet!
I wanted to offer you too.
Thank you.
May Allah bless you.
May it heal you.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the accursed satan.
In the name of Allah, the most merciful,
the most compassionate.
"And do not crave what
Allah has given some of you over others...
...Men will be rewarded
according to their deeds...
...and women ˹equally˺
according to theirs...
...Rather, ask Allah for His bounties...
...Surely Allah has ˹perfect˺
knowledge of all things.
[Surah An-Nisa - 1-176]
Allah Almighty speaks the truth.
Respect!
As-Salam Aleikum people of sharia.
As-Salam Aleikum people of Tariqa
As- Salam Aleikum
As-Salam Aleikum people of truth.
Tell me, the head of valiants.
What is the occupation of...
...the apprentice boy...
...that you want Ijazah?
He seeks your prayers under the sky...
He seeks your prayers on the grass...
The leatherman apprentice Ahmet.
He wanted to.
...came into your presence.
Not much left.
Your suffering will end.
You are going to Konya.
We'll send your Osman Bey after you.
Either alive...
...or dead.
Do not speak of my Bey with your
stinky mouth!
You'll see now!
Coward!
Untie us!
Ignoble dog!
Ignoble!
Untie us!
Brother!
Are you okay?
Keep your eyes open!
Do not let anyone near!
Did you think I would forget you?
Would I ever forget you?
I am always here.
Drink it.
This is Ahi Sherbet.
I want all of you to drink it.
May Allah bless you.
Thank you very much.
May it heal you, my valiants.
I want to offer to the vailants inside.
No.
There are captives inside.
Now it is time to get the Alps.
Let's go.
Kumral Abdal, bring Alps clothes.
Yes my Bey.
Come on.
Have this pocket.
Alps are going to Konya.
Get lost for a while.
It's Vizier Alam Shah's order!
Betrayer!
Betrayer dog!
Betrayers don't live long, Bahadir!
Eyvallah. (thanks)
Stop, not this way.
Take the back exit.
Eyvallah (okay.)
- Ignoble dog!
- Shame on you!
Osman Bey!
Yeah, Osman Bey.
You ignoble dog!
You sold your honor for gold!
You are going to pay for what
happened to my Alps.
Come here!
Tell me...
...are you the betrayer in the tribe?
Tell me!
I am not only the betrayer.
I caused Karayel's death as well.
Karayel!
Thank Allah, my Bey.
Brothers!
My Bey!
- My Bey, how is your wound?
- It's okay.
- Are you fine?
- We are fine, my Bey.
Let's go.
Welcome Osman Bey?
What's that? Are you going to ask us
to drop our weapons again?
Come here.
Soldiers!
Come.
This is for the spear.
And this is for all Alps!
Let's go alps!
Hey son.
We bless your body.
May Allah bless your soul.
Abide by sharia and justification
in trading.
Watch your hands and tongue.
Use your scales truthfully.
Kiss your master's hand.
Praise be.
Hadrat Vizier.
Osman Bey is here.
He took the Alps.
Osman!
Sheik Edebali.
We appreciate it all.
But we have an important issue.
We have to go immediately.
We are going to see each other
again eventually.
Eyvallah (sure).
Your arrival pleased us...
...Hadrat Vizier.
Salute for you.
Where are we going, my Bey?
Our destination is Inegol!
Let's go alps!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com